CONTACT

julianepoma@gmail.com Rosario, Argentina

PROFILE

Julián is an advanced Systems-Software Engineering student with a passion for learning and creating quality, functional code to solve problems. He enjoys designing projects and researching new technologies. His main interests are Web Development and aviation, and both complement each other really well.

LANGUAGES

Español - native Inglés - fluent, full professional proficiency

JULIÁN EMANUEL POMA

EXPERIENCE

Laravel 5 and VueJS 2 Developer

SGC S.A Rosario

December 2017 - Present

- In charge of the development of a lite-CRM system used to manage 5000 customers and the services offered.
- Managing the migration form the old databases.
- Integration of the new CRM system with the networks of the organization.
- Development of a billing system and a customer's side application.

Web UI Bootcamp

Globant Rosario

May 2017 - June 2017

Learned the basics of web development, API requests and Single Page

Applications.

EDUCATION

Systems-Software

Engineering

Universidad Tecnológica FRRO

April 2014 - Present

Expected Graduation 2018 Graduación esperada 2018

Cambridge English First

Certificate

IATEL

Rosario

Grade B

Relevant coursework:

- Data Mining
- Algorithms
- Web Development

PERSONAL PROJECTS

BetterReads

A fork of the known GoodReads. developed with the MEAN stack: MongoDB, Express and NodeJS serving a RESTful API, and Angular 6 providing the frontend. It offers full auth using JWT, files upload, protected routes and a material design style.

Fakestagram

A Progressive Web App clone of Instagram, which allows users to upload and share photos. It supports device camera access, localization and off-line synchronization.

SKILLS & KNOWLEDGE

Advanced Laravel 5 Angular 6 VueJS 2 **GIT**

Intermediate NodeJS

Google Firebase

MongoDB

Basic Python **PWAs**

SQL Databases



In /in/julianpoma



/julianpoma



julianpoma.com